thomascook.in 2019-03-25

# Privacy Policy - Privacy Policy Terms | Thomas Cook India

INTRODUCTION: 

This Privacy (“Policy”) applies to the securing and processing of personal data by TCIL (India). Ltd (hereinafter “TCIL” in connection with personal data provided by any person (“User”) who has purchased or intends to purchase or inquiries about any product(s) or service(s) made by TCIL through any of TCIL’s interface channels including website, mobile site and mobile app (collectively referred herein as “Sales Channels”). 

For the purpose of Privacy Policy:

  * References in this policy to “you” or “your” are references to ‘User’
  * References to “we”, “us” or “our” are references to ‘TCIL’
  * When you take part in surveys or provide us with feedback
  * References to “website” mean a reference to ‘website(s)’, ‘mobile site(s)’ and mobile app(s)

We respect your need to understand how and why information is being collected, used, disclosed, transferred and stored. Thus we have developed this Policy to familiarize you with our practices. This policy sets out the way in which we process your information when you use our Website or other digital platforms in accordance with applicable data protection laws. It is important that you read this policy together with any other policies we may provide on specific occasions when we are collecting or processing your personal data, so that you are fully aware of how and why we are using your personal data. This policy supplements the other notices and is not intended to override them. 

DEFINING CONTROLLER OF PERSONAL DATA

TYPE OF PERSONAL DATA WE COLLECT

MODES OF COLLECTING PERSONAL DATA

GROUNDS FOR PROCESSING OF DATA

COLLECTION AND USE OF NON-PERSONAL DATA

COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNOLOGIES

WITH WHOM YOUR PERSONAL DATA IS SHARED:

DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

PERMISSIONS REQUIRED FOR USING OUR MOBILE APPLICATIONS

INFORMATION PROTECTION AND SECURITY
